The closer you look, the less you’ll see.
Now You See Me is a thriller, crime film directed by Louis Leterrier.
An FBI agent and an Interpol detective track a team of illusionists who pull off bank
heists during their performances and reward their audiences with the money.
J. Daniel Atlas, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Merritt McKinney, played by Woody Harrelson.
Henley Reeves, played by Isla Fisher.
Jack Wilder, played by Dave Franco.
Dylan Rhodes, played by Mark Ruffalo.
Alma Dray, played by Mélanie Laurent.
Now You See Me is a 2013 American heist film directed by Louis Leterrier from a screenplay by
Ed Solomon, Boaz Yakin, and Edward Ricourt and a story by Yakin and Ricourt.
It is the first installment in the Now You See Me series.
The film features an ensemble cast of Jesse Eisenberg, Mark Ruffalo, Woody Harrelson, Mélanie
Laurent, Isla Fisher, Common, Dave Franco, Michael Caine, and Morgan Freeman.
The plot follows an FBI agent and an Interpol detective who track and attempt to bring to justice a team of magicians who
pull off bank heists and robberies during their performances and reward their audiences with the money.
The film premiered in New York City on May 21, 2013, before its official release
in the United States on May 31, 2013, by Summit Entertainment.
The film received mixed reviews with criticism being focused on the ending, but became a box
office success, grossing $351.7 million worldwide against a budget of $75 million.
The film won the People's Choice Award for Favorite Thriller Movie and also received nominations for the
Empire Award for Best Thriller and the Saturn Award for Best Thriller Film and Best Music.
A sequel, Now You See Me 2, was released on June 10, 2016.
A third installment, Now You See Me: Now You Don't,
was released on November 14, 2025.
The film explores themes of new york city, paris, france, escape, magic, bank.
The tone is intense.